You know, a very bad person
invented trigonometry.
Can I drive to school today?
What? I'm a good driver.
Have a good day.
Have fun.
See you guys later.
I'll let you drive.
Hey, so, you wanna go
for a climb after school?
Yeah, I was kinda thinking I might
go over to Brooke's after school.
How's that going with her, by the way?
I don't know.
Why don't you just tell her?
Does Brooke even know that you like her?
What if she likes Drew?
Then you know the score,
that she has bad taste.
- Hey. Where are you?
Yeah, I was driving myself to school.
Oh, God. Jason, this is
a little bit weird.
It should be you. You know this.
Don't worry about them. Just-- You do you.
What's that supposed to be?
You have a cat in a sealed box.
And also in the box,
we have a vial of poison,
Now, if there's no atomic decay,
the cat lives.
Before we look inside,
the atom exists in a superposition,
Which means what?
This guy had a thing for torturing cats.
and he had a thing
for understanding the universe.
The answer, for anybody who cares to know,
is that the atom in superposition
means that the cat is both alive
and it is dead.
His name's Woody Gwyn,
one of America's
great contemporary landscape masters.
- Let me get my stuff.
- I could paint that.
- You can do anything, babe.
I'm apartment hunting Friday,
if you wanna come.
I would love to,
but Friday is my training day.
My cycling time and my running time
aren't bad actually,
but my swimming really needs work.
And right now, I can't even imagine
doing them all back-to-back.
You know, there are less agonizing ways
for you to avoid your family.
- I'm just saying.
- I'm not avoiding them.
- So, when's the race?
Well, I think it would be foolish not to.
That's why I love you.
'Cause I'm an advocate
of opening more wine always?
That's the source
of your adoration for me?
Yeah, I think that's the only reason
we've made it this far.
Close your eyes.
Your phone's blowing up.
- Who is it?
and he's wondering where you are?
- I found out today.
Where is it happening?
Because he knows that if he picks
any place remotely far away, I'm not gonna show.
I'm glad you're having a good time. No.
You know he would show up for you.
You're having a little celebration
at my local bar, then it's probably - a desperate plea for my attention.
Your wife is a beautiful genius,
and I appreciate her.
Congratulations.
Could I
introduce you to a bunch of people?
The kind you don't really wanna meet.
And what do you do?
- I teach physics at Lakemont.
What exactly was the citation again?
And don't pretend
you haven't memorized it.
I owe you.
We're scientists. We sign on
to struggle and search our entire lives in anonymity, you know?
Congratulations.
It wasn't for some bullshit victory lap.
Jason, we already have the space.
I'm really gonna have to get back
to them actually.
if you don't do exactly what I say,
I will kill you.
Eyes on the road. Keep driving.
What's the passcode to your phone?
What kind of job?
He's starting a neurotech company
in San Francisco.
- What did you say?
- Well, I didn't give him an answer.
Take this exit.
Take off your clothes.
Start moving.
Down there.